<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Tech | Ethical Hacker]]></title>
  <link href="http://krishnaarava.github.io/blog/categories/tech/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://krishnaarava.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2014-06-03T17:09:57+05:30</updated>
  <id>http://krishnaarava.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Krishna Arava]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are You Not Happy With Your IT Job?]]></title>
    <link href="http://krishnaarava.github.io/blog/2011/02/19/i-met-some-of-my-buddies-yesterday/"/>
    <updated>2011-02-19T03:43:00+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://krishnaarava.github.io/blog/2011/02/19/i-met-some-of-my-buddies-yesterday</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<div class='post'>
I met some of my buddies yesterday. And one thing that is often common in conversations in these meetings is everyone tell's me about how much their job sucks in Indian IT consultancy companies. Most of these companies have poor standards, ethics and ridiculous work cultures. These so called professionals jobs are mere low end support / maintenance related roles. And <a href="http://www.google.com/search?sourceid=chrome&amp;client=ubuntu&amp;channel=cs&amp;ie=UTF-8&amp;q=why+enterprise+software+sucks%3F">enterprise software sucks</a>. <br/><br/>On the other side companies like Apple and Google have given power to developers. Developers can now write and monetize applications using <a href="https://market.android.com">Android Market</a>, <a href="https://chrome.google.com/webstore">Chrome Web store</a>, <a href="http://www.apple.com/iphone/apps-for-iphone/">Apple App Store</a>. Other places where developers / consultants can look for work on is <a href="freelancer.com">freelancer.com</a>. These are just few instances, there are millions of places on the internet where we can look for work. <br/><br/>I work for another Indian IT consultancy but I do enjoy technology as much as I can. I work most of free time on the internet. In the past I have done lot of work like building websites, jailbreaking iphones &amp; android phones, learning new concepts about networking and security. I have written my own operating system based on linux. My ambition is to join Google one day. <br/><br/>Here is how I will break it down learn something new:<br/><br/>1) The best way to start is to start <br/><br/>Yes, start with something you thought was interesting. It need not be about programming or something related to you current role. It could be something that you always baffled about. Like how does an operating system work /  What is hacking / How does internet work / What technologies is facebook using to support 600 million users?<br/><br/>Internet has all the answers. So keep browsing till you find answers (get a smartphone to browse the internet, it is very handy and productive). This will help you find to narrow down to your interests.<br/><br/>2) Choose your interest<br/><br/>Talk to your friends / colleagues to discuss about your new interests. They can help you choose and narrow down your options. Also you will get an insight into career's that are flourishing. <br/><br/>3) Plan for a course<br/><br/>While I dont recommend to going back to College / special tutorial classes, lectures such as <a href="http://ocw.mit.edu/courses/electrical-engineering-and-computer-science/6-00-introduction-to-computer-science-and-programming-fall-2008/video-lectures/">these</a> are available online. So use <a href="http://video.google.com">google search</a> to find lectures. Or borrow / rent books. Prepare a scheduled plan for your course.<br/><br/>You need to have strong will to stick to implement the plan. But this course will surely help you to learn and enjoy technology. Technology is fun for most home based hackers (I am one such). In due course it can be eventually turned into full time career. For one to become successful it takes years, so be patient my friend things will not happen overnight. <br/><br/>I can quote number of CEO's of startup in Silicon valley who have switched jobs and followed their interests / passion to become successful (<a href="http://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=2222522">like this one</a>).<br/><br/>So best of luck and share any information in comments below this post.</div>


<h2>Comments</h2>


<div class='comments'>
<div class='comment'>
<div class='author'>Lakshmi</div>
<div class='content'>
Hey Chaitanya....nice article!!!!</div>
</div>
<div class='comment'>
<div class='author'>Druthi</div>
<div class='content'>
Loved your posting and the way you keep up your interest!!! all the best with your future endeavors .... Its a quest for self satisfaction and it should take time....lekapothe em maza kada :)</div>
</div>
</div>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2Coolstuff Tips - Why Spend Money on Microsoft Office When You Have Openoffice]]></title>
    <link href="http://krishnaarava.github.io/blog/2010/02/12/time-and-again-many-of-my-friends-ask/"/>
    <updated>2010-02-12T14:05:00+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://krishnaarava.github.io/blog/2010/02/12/time-and-again-many-of-my-friends-ask</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<div class='post'>
Time and again many of my friends ask me these questions - Which Microsoft office version should they buy for their laptops? Which anti-virus to use?<br /><br />So I want to share something many of them dont know. We have free version of office from Sun Microsystems (Oracle bought Sun Microsystems recently) that can be downloaded from Internet for free. Free is absolutely free, you don't have to spend a penny! Still dont believe it?<br /><br />Please download the latest Openoffice 3.2 from the below link.<br /><br /><a href="http://download.openoffice.org/">http://download.openoffice.org/</a><br /><br />The product is compatible with Microsoft Documents and is pretty good. It is available for all the operating systems Windows, Linux and Mac OS. The product is also supported with security updates and patches.<br /><br />If you liked this tip, please do share it with your friends.</div>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2Coolstuff – Bollywood Channel on Youtube]]></title>
    <link href="http://krishnaarava.github.io/blog/2010/02/09/youtube-has-launched-exclusive/"/>
    <updated>2010-02-09T04:02:00+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://krishnaarava.github.io/blog/2010/02/09/youtube-has-launched-exclusive</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<div class='post'>
Youtube has launched exclusive bollywood channel. Right now the catalog does not have many movies, but in the near future we can expect something similar to Netflix. So stop burning CD's/copying movies from your friends just sit back and enjoy connect streamed in high resolution.<br /><br /><a href="http://www.youtube.com/movies?s=mvr&amp;b=18">http://www.youtube.com/movies?s=mvr&amp;b=18</a></div>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tata Consultancy Service Website Hacked]]></title>
    <link href="http://krishnaarava.github.io/blog/2010/02/07/techcrunch-is-reporting-that-tata/"/>
    <updated>2010-02-07T17:18:00+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://krishnaarava.github.io/blog/2010/02/07/techcrunch-is-reporting-that-tata</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<div class='post'>
Techcrunch is reporting that Tata Consultancy Services www.tcs.com website is hacked. It was similar to twitter DNS hack last year where the DNS entry of the owner's domain tcs.com was modified. <br /><br />Its very clear insurgents are taking "other routes" in disrupting economy.<br />Will we get to see similar attacks in cyber space now?<br /><br />Read from the below link for more details.<br /><br /><a href="http://www.techcrunch.com/2010/02/07/indian-it-giant-tata-consultancy-services-hacked/">http://www.techcrunch.com/2010/02/07/indian-it-giant-tata-consultancy-services-hacked/</a><br /><br />Update: Looks like the site is back to normal now.</div>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Striker Movie Now Available on Youtube]]></title>
    <link href="http://krishnaarava.github.io/blog/2010/02/06/new-striker-hindi-movie-starring/"/>
    <updated>2010-02-06T15:52:00+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://krishnaarava.github.io/blog/2010/02/06/new-striker-hindi-movie-starring</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<div class='post'>
The new Striker Hindi movie Starring Siddarth is now availble on Youtube for Rent.<br /><br /><a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7WVcB-o-Q1I#">http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7WVcB-o-Q1I#</a><br /><br />It costs 4.99$ dollars to rent the movie. Go ahead and watch it!</div>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
